funkyjunkinteriors.net 2019-12-13

# GDPR & Your DataFunky Junk Interiors

.

Hey, hi!

So, there are a bunch of new data privacy rules that have come into play if you are a visitor that requires GDPR compliance as of May 25, 2018.

If you are in the USA or Canada, this doesn’t apply to you. Sorry for all the extra hoopla.

However, my message below is indeed applicable to anyone…

Any info you leave on this site is only used to perform the tasks you request it to. I protect your info under password protection, and keep ONLY what is absolutely required to perform the tasks you wish to perform, so your reader experience is a good one.

And you only get what you ask for. So for instance, if you want to sign up for an emailed blog post update because you just want the emailed blog post update, that’s what you’ll get. Everything involved is spelled out before you click SUBMIT so you can make an informed choice.

Thank-you for your visits, email subscriptions (and optional un-subscriptions too), comments, linkups to weekend DIY parties, and for trusting this site to respect and take good care of your info.

If that’s all you need, we’re good. Really, nothing has changed over here other than a whole bunch more words added so you’re more aware how what is being used how. Email me at donna@funkyjunkinteriors.net if you require help.

So let’s go have some DIY fun!

For those that wish to hear all the more legal nitty gritty details, it’s all below…

* * *

**Privacy Policy   / How we collect your data / What we do with it**

Funky Junk Interior’s privacy policy was updated on May 4th 2018.

* * *

**We collect and process personal data**

When visiting [funkyjunkinteriors.com](http://funkyjunkinteriors.com/) your personal data may be collected. Most of our web pages contain information which does not require any personal information from the web site visitor. However, in some cases we need to collect and store personal data in order to provide services or information that you request from the website. At Funky Junk Interiors we collect information regarding your website behaviour and your communication and interaction on this site. This information may be connected to existing personal data that has been stored for a specified and defined purpose.

* * *

**How Funky Junk Interiors collects and processes your personal data**

Funky Junk Interiors controls all of the personal data that you share with us when you:

    ~Visit our web site and accept cookies  
    ~Contact us by form or by e-mail  
    ~Are a customer, partner or have entered into a process to become customer or partner  
    ~Sign up for any of our notifications and newsletters  
    ~Download material that requires you to submit a form  
    ~Subscribe to our blog

  Your personal information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, nor given to any other company for any reason whatsoever without your consent. The only exception to this might be the express purpose of delivering an ordered product or service requested by the customer.

* * *

**Why we process personal data**

Funky Junk Interiors processes personal data and relevant information that is needed to properly provide our services and/or enhance the experience of visiting our sites. We need to process personal data in order to administrate user accounts, manage notifications, digital marketing and re-marketing. If you no longer want to receive digital notifications and/or marketing, you can unsubscribe. There is an unsubscribe button at the bottom of each email.

We store non-sensitive data about our customer. For example, first and last name, email address, comments.

Some additional ways that Funky Junk Interiors may collect and store your data includes but is not limited to the following:
